Once a year she rises. For one season she reigns.
Snow Queen is a adventure, family, fantasy film directed by David Wu.
Since a bitter winter storm stole the life of Gerda's mother, she and her
father have sadly continued to run the remote hotel they call home.
Lonely and isolated, Gerda's only joy is Kai, the handsome bellboy.
A mysterious guest with an icy stare arrives at the hotel
one night, wrapped in fur and diamonds.
By daybreak, the "Snow Queen" has vanished with Kai!
Gerda embarks on a journey of morphing seasons, fantastical creatures, and
long-frozen mysteries in a desperate quest to find her stolen love.
Snow Queen, played by Bridget Fonda.
Kai, played by Jeremy Guilbaut.
Gerda, played by Chelsea Hobbs.
Wolfgang, played by Robert Wisden.
Minna, played by Wanda Cannon.
Robber Girl, played by Meghan Black.
Snow Queen is a 2002 made-for-television film produced by Hallmark Entertainment and directed
by David Wu based on the 1844 story The Snow Queen by Hans Christian Andersen.
Also known as The Winter Witch, the film stars Bridget Fonda as the title
character and Chelsea Hobbs as her rival and the story's heroine, Gerda.
The film originally aired on Hallmark Channel as a two-part miniseries, but has
since been released as a full-length film on DVD in the United States.
The DVD was released in the United Kingdom on November 9,
2009 and in Australia on September 2, 2011.
This was Bridget Fonda's last acting role before her retirement.
The tone is thought_provoking.